https://storyoftheuniverse.org/privacy/

CENTER FOR THE STORY OF THE UNIVERSE PRIVACY POLICY
The Center for the Story of the Universe (The Center) is dedicated to protecting your privacy as you use our web site. Our policy is that no personal information will be collected about you unless you choose to provide it.
The Center may collect e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable data about visitors when such data is voluntarily submitted. For example, our site uses forms for visitors to request more information or purchase products. Contact information from the form is used to send orders and information about The Center to our visitors. Financial information is used to bill visitors in connection with their orders.
The Center makes every effort to insure the secure collection and transmission of sensitive user information using industry accepted data collection and encryption methodologies. Please be advised, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. The Center is committed to protecting users’ personal information, but cannot guarantee or warrant the security of this information when it is transmitted over the Internet to or through The Center’s web site. Transmission of such information is therefore at the risk of the user.
The Center does not sell, rent or otherwise knowingly disclose such user information outside the organization except as follows:
When disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with the operations of the web site or the rights (including property rights) or safety of other users or third parties or of The Center.
When The Center reasonably believes that disclosure is required by law or to comply with legal process served on the Center.
Our site contains links to other sites. Please remember that our privacy policy does not apply to other sites and that we cannot be responsible for their privacy policies.
Remember that no one can guarantee the complete security of information transmitted over the Internet. Therefore, you should be careful about the personal information which you provide to us or any other site.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, your records or your dealings with this site, please contact us at espinosa [at] brianswimme [dot] org.
Home
|
About
|
Store
|
Programs
|
Contact
© 2003-2020 Center for the Story of the UniversePrivacy | Legal | Contact Us Photos on this site courtesy of HubbleSite and NASA's Astronomy Picture of the Day
Credit Card Merchant Services
